Bart levy I'm confused why did you bring
me to the lands blindfolded are we going
to have some kinky sex in the toy aisle
again [ __ ] do you remember when you
told me you loved the song
fruit salad by the Wiggles yes I
remember that I've always loved the
Wiggles well I thought I'd bring you
here so we could make our own fruit
salad together doesn't that just sound
scrumptious we could even pick our own
fruits and veggies Oh Bartleby that
sounds wonderful
uh-huh I knew that you would like it
daddy knows how to please his bitch man
Bartleby spot is so big what I would
give to squeeze it right now it's a
shame we're out in public right now
because if we were in my bedroom oh yes
uh-huh Oh Beach we're not even in the
storm yet and you're already admiring
the watermelons or other my butt cheeks
this cucumber looks good nice and firm
like my sweaty butt cheeks after a
workout
wouldn't you agree Beach I'll put this
in the shopping cart it will be a fine
addition to a fruit salad
haha Oh Bart levy that's not the
shopping cart you just put your cucumber
in my butt no but they said I was
putting it in the shopping cart
hey bitch which do you think would make
a fruit salad more delightful apples or
oranges I can't decide they both look
like your cute little butt cheeks ha ha
oh come on Bart levy you're the richest
man on earth just get both oh I suppose
you're right
ha ha ha sometimes I forget just how
rich I am think fast
uh-huh
sorry about that which I forgot just how
strong my throwing arm was you can put
that banana in the shopping cart or
stick it in your big buttt and sneak it
out of here I don't give a [ __ ]
something tells me we won't be putting
it into the fruit salad anyway